diehardfans.com 2012-10-03

# Privacy Policy - DieHardFans

**100% Confidentiality**

When you use Diehardfans.com you are giving us permission to use your personal details, as supplied voluntarily by yourself, in accordance to the policy below.

As a website, DieHardFans.com is 100% committed to protecting your personal information. In order to do this and thus eradicate any concerns you may have, we have taken extensive steps to guarantee the confidentiality and protection of all the information you provide us with, including details such as your name, address, e-mail address, telephone number, credit card number and card verification number.

**Sensitive Personal Data**

This information is classed as “sensitive personal data” under law. We can assure you that your sensitive personal data will never, under any circumstances, be unwillingly disclosed to any third parties. We will only pass on information after receiving original written consent from you, personally. All the information we hold will be held securely in accordance with our security policy and the law.

Our employees are aware of the privacy guidelines, and thus employed to maintain the confidentiality of your information.

**Secure Socket Layer**

Here at Diehardfans.com we use the latest, most secure and best encryption technology to protect your credit card and sensitive personal data. We use the industry standard 128-bit Secure Socket Layer (SSL) encryption when you place an order online, for which we bear a certificate on the homepage.

We will only use your personal information to contact and correspond with you in order to respond best to your inquiries, to process transactions and payments and enhance your use of the Website.

This policy is applicable only to information collected from you during your visit to this website. We will display a prominent notice on this website's home page whenever this privacy policy is updated or changed and you should check our privacy policy periodically.
